<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Know Your Computer Scientists</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Settings</string>
    <string name="scientist1_name">Alan Turing</string>
    <string name="content_description">Here is the picture of a famous computer scientist.</string>
    <string name="scientist1_description">In four inadequate words Alan Turing appears 
        now as the founder of computer science, the originator of the dominant technology 
        of the late twentieth century, but these words were not spoken in his own lifetime, 
        and he may yet be seen in a different light in the future.
        
        His greatest work was: the idea of the Universal Turing Machine. 
        The concept of \'the Turing machine\' is like that of \'the formula\' or \'the equation\'; 
        there is an infinity of possible Turing machines, each corresponding to a different 
        \'definite method\' or algorithm. But imagine, as Turing did, each particular algorithm 
        written out as a set of instructions in a standard form. Then the work of interpreting 
        the instructions and carrying them out is itself a mechanical process, and so can itself 
        be embodied in a particular Turing machine, namely the Universal Turing machine.
        A Universal Turing machine can be made do what any other particular Turing machine
        would do, by supplying it with the standard form describing that Turing machine. 
        One machine, for all possible tasks.
        
        </string>
    <string name="scientist2_description">Jonathan Gillette, better known as why the lucky stiff 
        (often abbreviated to Why or _why) , was until 2009 a prolific writer, cartoonist, artist
 and computer programmer notable for his work with the Ruby programming language.
 He was known as one of the most unusual, and beloved, computer programmers
 in the world before he abruptly disappeared from public view.  Along with Yukihiro 
 Matsumoto and David Heinemeier Hansson, he was seen as a key figure in the Ruby 
 community. _why was the keynote speaker at RailsConf in 2006.
    On 19 August 2009, his online presence was drastically truncated; his accounts on Twitter 
    and GitHub were shut down, along with many of his personally maintained sites. 
    His projects have since been collected and centralized on the whymirror GitHub account.
	</string>
    <string name="scientist2_name">Jonathan Gillette</string>

</resources>
